{
    "subject": "resource/Lene_Lai",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Taipei",
    "human_readable": "Lene Lai was born in Taipei.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8532331585884094,
            "question": "Where was Lene Lai born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7594277262687683,
            "question": "When was Lene Lai born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3163580894470215,
            "question": "Who are some famous people from Taipei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2853861451148987,
            "question": "Does Lene Lai have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2746826410293579,
            "question": "What is Taipei known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2357257902622223,
            "question": "Is there anything else we know about Lene Lai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20742367208003998,
            "question": "What language is spoken in Taipei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1785939484834671,
            "question": "What kind of cultural events are popular in Taipei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17161235213279724,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Taipei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14358332753181458,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Taipei?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lene Lai was born in Taipei.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8471_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Taipei?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8471_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of cultural events are popular in Taipei?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8471_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language is spoken in Taipei?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8471_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8471_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. In fact, multiple documents (60.txt, 63.txt) mention that Lene Lai was born on June 6, 1989 (or 6 June 1989) in Taipei, Taiwan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Lene Lai was born on June 6, 1989, in Taipei, Taiwan, which supports the statement that Lene Lai was born in Taipei."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}